propertydalal.com 2011-01-21

# Privacy Policy – propertydalal.com

| Who We Are  
---  
'We' are Propertydalal.com, Realty (P) LTD, Suite # 110, BPTP Park Centra Sector 31, Opp. 32nd Milestone, National Highway 8, Gurgaon, Haryana, India. 122001  
1\. Introduction   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you via www.propertydalal.com (referred to below as "this Site"). Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this Site and any services we offer via this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site.

If you have any queries or comments about the policy or our use of your personal information, please get in touch with us by emailing us at mail@propertydalal.com or writing to The Privacy Manager at Propertydalal.com, 628 Galleria Towers, DLF Phase IV, Gurgaon. In general, we use the information we collect about you to:

  * help our members provide more personalised services to you 

  * provide information services to relevant third parties 

  * improve the features and services we offer 

  * support our own marketing and promotion efforts.

2\. Personal information collected  
When you visit, register or use the services on this Site, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including your name and your contact details. We may also collect information about how you use this Site including your searches, the properties you look at, agents or developers you contact and the contents of the emails you send to them. Finally, we may also collect information from any correspondance that you have with us.   
3\. Information collected and use  
Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of this Site and to supply the services and features that you have requested. We may aggregate the information to identify patterns which we can use in our marketing and to help us develop, administer, support and improve our services and features.

In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to this Site or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to email you with details about any other products or services which we offer which may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please email us at [mail@propertydalal.com](mailto:mail@propertydalal.com) and tell us.

The following features, by their nature, require and make use of personally identifiable information.  
  
4\. Sending emails  
The information that you complete on the 'contact agent' forms on this Site is recorded by us and is sent to the agent that you wish to contact. This helps them provide you with a more personalised service. We also send the agent details of your last search to help them find property that matches your requirements more closely.  
5\. Email a Friend  
When you use the 'email a friend' feature of this Site we record which properties you have been sent to the friend solely so that we can track the popularity of those properties. We record the other details provided in the email for internal monitoring of the service. We will NOT add any information collected in this manner to our mailing lists to protect you and the recipient's privacy.   
6\. Registering with us  
If you register with us, we save the details you provide and use them to enable us to personalise the service we offer to you. You can update 'your details' at any time via the site. When you are signed in, we automatically pre-fill your saved details on the "contact agent" forms should you wish to use this element of the service we offer to you.   
7\. Saving properties  
If you register with us and 'save properties' you are interested in, we can identify which properties you have saved. We do not make this individual information available to our member agents or third parties.   
8\. Using the 'email updates'  
If you register with us and use the 'your email updates' feature to receive notification when new properties matching your criteria are added to this Site, we record the settings you use and which properties have been sent to you. We do not make any information about any property that has been sent to you available to our member agents or third parties. If you are signed in when you send an email to an estate agent, we include your settings to help the estate agent to provide more personalised services to you.  
9\. Who has access to the information you provide or we collect  
We retain access to all personal information that we have collected from you. 

When our service is available via the websites of our partners, those partners may have access to your information. Their use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any other websites, even if you access them using links from this Site or if you can access this Site or use our services from them. We therefore recommend that you check the policy of each site that you visit and make sure that you are comfortable with the terms of such policies before providing any personal information.

If you have consented on 'your details' page or the appropriate email form, we may provide any of the information we collect to carefully screened third parties to contact you regarding products or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted by these third parties in the future, please email us at mail@propertydalal.com and tell us. 

If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. 

If we offer a service to you from the Site that is provided by a third party we may have to pass your information to them in order to deliver the service. By using such services you consent to us providing your information to the third party. We may also use third parties to provide services on our behalf which may include processing (but not using themselves) your information e.g. to complete partial addresses or to augment the information we hold about you. In either case, we will not pass your data to anyone who is not also registered with the Data Protection Act or is not subject to these or similar provisions in our contract with them and we will not allow the third party to use your information commercially without your consent. 

We will not otherwise disclose, sell or distribute your information to any third party without your permission unless we are required to do so by law.  
  
10\. Access to, changing or removing the information we hold  
Registered users of this Site can update their information, change settings or cancel their membership on their 'your details' page once signed in. 

Non-registered and registered users of this Site can request we provide them with a copy of the personally identifiable information we hold via mail@propertydalal.com. You may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that such information is accurate and kept up-to-date. We may charge a small administration fee to cover the data search, preparation and delivery.   
  
11\. Cookies and tracking  
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in the hard drive of your computer by your browser. Your browser will have the option to prevent websites using cookies (your browser's help screen or manual will tell you how to do this), but please note that this may reduce the functionality of this Site and other websites. 

Like all websites, our servers automatically record 'log files' containing information about the volume and characteristics of our website traffic e.g. IP address, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site. We use log files to build pictures of how our site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. We cannot identify you from your log files.  
  
Security, storage and transfer of information  
We follow strict security procedures to ensure that your personal information is not damaged, destroyed, or disclosed to a third party without your permission (unless they are providing services as outlined in the 'who has access to your information' section above) and to prevent unauthorised access to it. The computers that store the information are kept in a secure facility with restricted physical access and we use secure firewalls and other measures to restrict electronic access. If we are working with third parties we will require them to have in place similar measures to protect your information. 

All of the information we collect or record is restricted to our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. We will explicitly ask you when we need information to identify you. We may require you to co-operate with our security checks before we disclose information to you. You can update the personal information that you give us at any time by viewing your details page.

We will retain your information for a reasonable period or for as long as is required by law.  
  
Changes to the policy  
We may change this policy from time to time as we add new services or features or in response to changes in the law or our commercial arrangements. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this Site.
